Satan 's Slave
Mother .
Tomi .
You haven 't gone to sleep yet , ma 'am ?
Mr. Karto , don 't scare me like that .
Is something wrong , ma 'am ?
No , everything 's fine .
Tomi .
Good morning , Dad .
- Is Tomi still asleep ? - Yes .
Dad ,
last night I saw Tomi .
Tomi ?
What do you mean ?
I mean Tomi went to bed late last night .
Dad , I 'm going to mom 's grave and then to a friend 's house .
At this hour ?
- Eat your breakfast first . - I 'm not hungry . Maybe later .
I 'm heading out .
Rita ,
your mom just passed away , don 't come back too late .
Alright , Dad .
Good morning , Mom .
Mom ,
I pray that God
forgives all your sins ,
and takes care of you by his side .
Be happy and peaceful always , Mother .
I 'm going to leave now .
Tomi ?
Tomi !
That 's Tomi .
Hello , Tomi .
- Hi . - Hello .
How are you ?
Where did you go ?
- I 'm sorry about your mother . - I 'm sorry too .
You have to take care of yourself .
With your mom gone , you have to stay strong
and not lose hope .
It 's all God 's will .
I 've gone through this too .
I stopped going to school
and almost went crazy .
Luckily , there was a fortune teller who helped me .
Fortune teller ?
Yes . She told me
that after my mother 's death ,
I didn 't need to be sad .
Because
good fortune is waiting for you ,
and all your wishes will be fulfilled .
Give me the address , Gi .
I forgot it ,
but I 'm sure you can go to any fortune teller .
The Black King .
This means your life is full of darkness .
Red Ace .
There 's an image of a coffin .
Do you know what that means ?
It must mean that you lost your mother .
That 's right .
How did you know ?
The coffin doesn 't only represent you ,
but your entire family . Their lives are in danger .
What ?
You have to be careful .
Protect yourself with black magic .
Tomi .
Tomi , what 's going on with you ?
Can 't you see I 'm concentrating ?
What do you want ?
What are you reading ?
You 've been acting weird the last few days .
Why did you stare at me in the cemetery ?
You 're not the only one who lost mom .
We all did .
We 've all lost someone we really loved .
Stop whatever you 're doing right now .
Tomi .
Why are you looking at me like that ?
Tomi !
- Hello ? - Is this Tomi 's house ?
That 's right . Who 's this ?
- Hello ? - This is Tomi 's house ?
Yeah . Who 's this ?
Hello ? Hello ?
Who is this ?
Shit !
- What do you want ? - Calm down , ma 'am .
If this is Tomi 's house , I 'm very glad .
This is Tomi 's house . What do you want ?
Don 't you dare disturb us again .
Jerks ! Idiots !
Tomi , what 's wrong with you ?
Good afternoon .
Why ?
Why 's everyone shocked ?
I thought it was someone else .
Tomi , what 's wrong with your nose ?
Herman , I 'm glad you 're here .
What 's the problem ?
Why don 't you sit down first .
Herman , since mother passed away ,
a lot of things have been happening in this house .
Weird things .
Herman ?
By the way , do you believe in Satan ?
Satan ?
Satan ? I believe Satan exists .
And he will go to people whose faith isn 't strong .
Like you and me .
Stop joking around , I 'm serious .
What 's wrong ?
Herman , I think ...
I saw Tomi talking to someone who looked like mom last night .
- Where ? - In this house .
Listen , Rita ...
I don 't really understand ,
but people say that 40 days after someone dies ,
their spirit can still wander the house .
You 're scaring me .
Sorry , Rita .
I didn 't come hereto scare you ,
but ...
I want you to come to a party .
Thank you , Mr. Munarto . I hope this business will be successful .
And not just a small success , but a really big one .
Our project is in line with the government 's mission .
We 'll build new houses for the community
and increase their standard of living .
Yes .
Alright ,
we won 't take any more of your time .
Remember Mr. Munarto , there is a deadline .
Oh , yes .
Since your wife just passed away
and your children need a caregiver at home ,
may I help you find a housekeeper ?
Thank you ,
but Dewi will take care of that .
Alright .
We 'll head out now . Good afternoon .
Good afternoon .
Are you going to Herman 's party ?
He 's coming to pick me up .
He said there 's a lot of good food there ,
so I 'm not eating at home .
Oh ,
I 've called an agency to find a housekeeper .
Someone who can take proper care of this place
and clean up all this mess .
That might be her .
I got it .
Good evening . Is this Mr. Munarto 's house ?
Yes .
I 'm the housekeeper from the agency .
I was requested yesterday .
This is the letter from the agency .
What 's the matter , Tomi ?
Oh , we were just talking about you . Please come in .
She 's from the agency , Dad .
Why have you come at this late hour ?
Have you brought your clothes ?
Yes , I have .
I 'm sorry , I just found out this evening .
We 're a family of three .
This is Rita and Tomi .
What 's your name ?
- Darminah . - Please show Darminah her room .
Right this way .
Thank you .
Karto !
Rita ,
let me get out .
No , Herman .
That old man is getting lazy .
Karto !
I 'll get out here .
Okay , goodnight .
Night .
Why did you lock the gate ?
I 've told you again and again , if I 'm not back , don 't lock the gate .
But I didn 't lock the gate .
You 're getting forgetful .
If you 're tired of this job , just tell us .
I 'm not tired at all .
I 've been working here for a long time .
Ma 'am ,
did you go to another party ?
It 's none of your business where I go . Why do you care ?
I mean ,
we just lost someone we loved .
It 's better for us to pray and send blessings for our loved one .
Karto ,
stop trying to cover up your mistake by lecturing me .
I 'm not a child .
Keys !
Are you awake , Darminah ?
Come in .
There 's someone who wants to meet you .
Who is it ?
He says he knows you .
And that it 's personal and very important .
Dewi ,
I 've told you over and over again ,
if it 's not business related , whoever it is ,
please just tell them I 'm busy .
I don 't discuss personal stuff at the office .
They can come to my house .
Alright , sir .
I 'm sorry , but ...
Mr. Munarto is very busy .
He 'd be happy to meet you at his house .
Alright .
Please tell Mr. Munarto I 'll go to his house .
Good afternoon .
Kill him ! Kill him ! Kill him !
No ! Please ! Please don 't kill me !
Kill him ! Kill him !
No ! No !
Kill him ! Kill him ! Kill him !
No !
Go away ! Please ! Please go away ! Don 't kill me !
- Tomi ? - No !
Tomi ? Tomi ?
Leave ! Go away !
Tomi , what 's going on ?
- No ! - Tomi !
No ! Leave !
Dad !
Tomi ,
from now on
you 're not allowed to play with these things .
You 'll go insane .
It 's true , Tomi . Don 't mess around with black magic .
It 's better if you say your prayers and send blessings for your mother .
- Karto . - Yes , sir ?
Get rid of all this .
Burn it .
Yes , sir .
I 'll be late getting back home tonight .
I want you home early .
Sir ?
There 's a guest who wants to meet you .
Who ?
He said he came to the office ,
but you told him to come here .
It 's personal .
Tell him I 'm not feeling well .
He can come back later .
Alright , sir .
Dad ,
this place doesn 't feel like home anymore
without mom in it .
Yes Dad , I feel the same way . I don 't even want to be here .
Don 't say that .
Darminah would be all alone here .
What 's wrong , Karto ? ls your asthma getting worse ?
I don 't think I can
handle it anymore .
Have you gone to the doctor ?
I want to go
and be
with the Father .
Take this and go to the doctor .
And stop talking about leaving this world .
Dying isn 't a good thing .
Thank you .
Now go get some rest .
Good morning , uncle .
- Is Rita home ? - Yes .
How 's college going ?
Not so great .
I 'm thinking of working at my father 's business .
That 's disappointing .
Hello .
This is Darminah .
She 's the new caretaker .
Herman .
Darminah , please get us some drinks .
Rita , that 's the look of death .
Quiet .
Seriously ,
there 's something about that look .
- And ... - Stop it .
Herman ?
I 'm sure this house has ghosts .
I 'm really confused .
Why ?
I 'm scared that my mother 's spirit is still here .
That 's the reason I 'm here .
I have the address for a very powerful shaman .
I 'm sure he can get rid of all the spirits haunting this house .
Are you sure , Herman ?
Yes .
On top of that ,
he can make sure your mother 's spirit is at peace in the other world .
Don 't talk to anyone about this .
I 'm going there tomorrow .
Yeah .
Karto !
How dare you ?
Get out of here right now .
I 'm sorry , I didn 't mean to intrude .
I wanted to clean .
Dewi , come here .
Yes , sir ?
Handoko will be here soon . Where 's his file ?
Still being analyzed at the data bureau .
- Can you tell them to hurry up ? - Of course .
And sir , the guest that was here last time , is here again .
I told him that you 're busy .
What did he say ?
He looked very disappointed .
However , he did say that you should not only focus on
building physical infrastructure ,
but also focus on spirituality and religion for the family .
How dare he ?
I don 't need religious lectures from him .
This is also good .
You 're too young to read that book .
You look afraid and uncertain .
Take it .
Get closer to God .
Pray and recite the holy book .
I don 't know how to pray .
My family doesn 't pray .
Your body , or any house , will be easily occupied by the devil ,
if you 're not close to God ,
and don 't abide by his rules .
Do it now . Before it 's too late .
Stop that .
Karto !
Where 's Karto ?
He 's not inside .
Karto !
- Excuse us , sir . - Thank you .
Fate has not been good to you , Karto .
What do you mean ?
I mean , I sent the order already .
- Okay . - Don 't get upset again .
Never mind . Don 't worry about it .
- See you later . - Yeah , sure .
Yes , hello ?
That 's right .
What ?
Where ?
What 's wrong , Rita ?
Herman was involved in an accident , Dad .
- He 's dead . - What ?
- Good afternoon . - Afternoon .
- Where 's the morgue ? - Over there .
- Thank you . - Yeah .
Who are you looking for ?
I 'm looking for the accident victim from this afternoon .
- Male ? - Yes .
His name is Herman .
That 's him .
This is him , ma 'am .
Tomi ?
I 'm very confused .
Don 't you find Herman and Karto 's deaths tragic ?
They were both such nice people .
Rita ,
I can 't help but think of Karto .
He told me to learn how to pray ,
and now he 's gone .
Herman died while he was looking
for a shaman to get rid of the ghosts in this house .
Stop talking about ghosts .
When I was praying ,
I was disturbed .
I 'm going to sleep .
Tomi , open the door ! Tomi , open the door !
Dad , open the door ! Open the door !
No ! No , Herman !
Darminah ! Darminah !
How are you feeling , Rita ?
I 'm fine , Dad .
Thank God .
Dad ?
I have a request .
Will you fulfill it ?
Since when have I refused your requests ?
Dad ...
Tomi and I have been disturbed by restless spirits in this house .
Please call a shaman .
Shaman ?
I don 't believe in any of that stuff .
It 's all myths .
But ...
If it 'll make you feel better ,
alright ,
I 'll do it .
To the God of the seven worlds ,
God of the seven seas ,
protect this house from the grip of evil !
Destroy all the evil spirits , and all the lusts of the devil , jinn , and angels !
Leave ! Leave !
Go !
Leave , devil ! Go !
Be gone from here , evil !
Leave ! Leave ! Leave !
Don 't trouble this house ! Leave now or I will destroy you !
Leave ! Now !
Rise ...
Rise up from your grave .
Rise , Mawarni !
Rise .
Come out .
Rise and follow my commands !
Rise up !
Destroy your family !
Rise up ! Rise up !
Rise up !
Rise !
No !
Don 't disturb my mother !
Kill him !
Help !
Dad , open the door !
Dad !
Open the door !
Dad ! Rita !
What 's wrong , Tomi ?
Dad !
Dad , she 's brought mom out of the grave !
- I saw it myself ! - Who is she ?
Who did it ?
Her ! She has to get out of here now !
She 's going to destroy our family ! She 's brought all this upon us !
Calm down , Tomi . Calm down .
Speak clearly .
- Darminah . - Darminah ?
What about her ?
Sis ,
she 's also brought Herman and Karto 's dead bodies back from the grave !
- Tomi . - It 's true , Dad .
When Darminah entered this house , evil spirits came in too .
Quiet !
I don 't believe any of this .
It 's all nonsense .
Let 's go and check her room .
Let 's go .
Good evening .
I 'm sure , Dad ! I saw it myself !
- I 'm not ... - Tomi !
From now on , I don 't want you going out at night .
Do you understand ?
Come .
Let it go , Tomi .
Don 't worry too much about last night .
No .
I know what I saw !
I 'm not lying !
Maybe it was someone who looked like Darminah .
No !
She 's the devil !
She can be anywhere .
She 'll destroy our family .
We have to check mom 's grave .
What do you mean ?
Let 's dig .
Quickly , Tomi .
Yes .
Keep going . Faster .
There . All done .
Now we have to open it .
Quiet . Dad 's asleep .
Okay .
Where have you been at this hour ?
We were ...
Where did you go ?
We went to mom 's grave .
Your mother 's grave ?
What were you doing ?
Come on .
I ...
I wanted to be sure about what I saw last night .
You dug up mom 's grave ?
Yes .
Are you crazy ?
Your mind really has been possessed by the devil !
Change your clothes !
Come on !
Dad ?
I 'm scared .
I want to sleep with you .
Tomi .
Tomi ! Open up !
Tomi !
Open up !
Dad !
Tomi ?
Mawarni ?
No .
My wife is dead .
Go back to your world .
No .
No . No .
No , Mawarni .
No .
No ! No !
Dad !
Tomi !
- Dad ! - Rita !
Kill them all .
Wait !
Who are you ?
I will kill you all ,
one by one ,
and I will make you my slaves .
What have we done to deserve this ?
I destroy people with no faith ,
nonbelievers like you !
We will always come for people like you ,
who use religion as a cover .
You 're evil !
Get out of my house !
Get out !
We won 't leave .
Not until you come with us .
Watch out !
Run !
Go !
Stay behind me .
Watch out !
Barbaric !
Don 't try to defend them !
I will destroy you too !
You can try to destroy us .
God is great !
People of faith ,
come to Islam ,
and don 't follow the path of Satan .
Your true enemy is Satan .
The righteous path
is to follow God .
Religion is my enemy !
Destroy them !
I beg for protection from God Almighty against Satan .
He is omnipresent and the protector of all beings .
The only one that takes care of all his children .
He does not sleep , and uses all his power above and below .
We only feel protected with Him next to us .
Without his blessings , nothing happens .
God knows what 's in front of and behind him ,
while others are blinded and know nothing .
We are his children .
His kingdom covers the sky and the Earth ,
but he is not burdened by the care of both .
He is the creator and seer of everything .
The End